<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ElCafeCartel</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="the_project">

    </string>
    <string name="project_1">Welcome to Valle de la Muerte, Home to El Cafe Cartel. El Cafe Cartel is a web 3 lifestyle brand with three core components.\nArt💀 Community🌴 Coffee☕️</string>
    <string name="project_art">El Cafe Cartel is bringing the art of Legenday artist funksteady to Near Protocol. The primary utility of this project is our art. Our holders will be proud to wear our PFP’s which will be composed of some of the finest art you can find on blockchain. With lore, branding and artwork themes of South American Cartels and Mexican folklore. By holding a limited release piece from the Wanted Dead or Alive collection you will be able to benefit from the sales of future 1/1 art auctions. Through our utility token $CAFE you will be able to unlock future cartel artwork by funksteady through a gamified experience. Burn $CAFE to receive randomised packages which could reward you with in game items that will be needed in the future. One day you might even own a piece of Valle de la Muerte.</string>
    <string name="project_community">Join our community and immerse yourself in the lore and history of Valle de la Muerte. “When the cartel rises, we all rise together.” This phrase is front and centre of everything we aim to achieve. We are dedicated to bringing value to our community members and lifting them up as we go on this journey together. But we won’t stop there. By joining the Cartel you are embarking on something bigger. Our community will be empowered, but we will also empower communities. A portion of profits will go towards funding El Café Trust. The trust will support underprivileged communities and environmental initiatives. This will not be a token gesture, we hope to affect meaningful action.</string>
    <string name="project_cafe">We love NFT’s and we love coffee. Our team are dedicated to building an exclusive coffee brand. We are exploring various partnerships who share our vision of supporting sustainable coffee production from the farm to the shop. And yes, our aim is for you to be able to buy coffee with $CAFE. Come for the art, stay for the vibes. $CAFE or LEAD.</string>
    <string name="about_team">Benny Blanco | Co-Founder | Project Lead \nCoolaaron | Co-Founder Coffee aficionado \nFunksteady | Co-Founder &amp; Legendary artist \nMacca | Co-Founder | Partnerships and Collabs \nSumo | Co-Founder | Alpha and Socials \nMasa | Co-Founder | PR &amp; Sales Executive \nSolpeppe | Lead Mod and Vibe Guru \nDleer.ious | Tokenomics advisor Maths genius \nHack-a-Chain | Developer \nGoudvis | Project Advisor Mara Co-founder \nRavi | Project Advisor Monke Art Collector</string>
</resources>